With Inyaba in tow and
a new carriage to boot,
JoJo and crew arrived in
the coastal town of Karachi,
Pakistan's industrial and financial
center located in the Indus River Delta.
Thank you.
Take it out with vision to turn around.
Oh, hey, a Donner Kebab joint.
Let's stop and get something to eat.
The Donner Kebab.
It's been called the
hamburger of the Middle East.
A slab of meat is placed on a spit,
its outer layer roasting as it turns.
Before long, the meat is cooked,
sliced, and served with any
number of sides and condiments.
Excuse me, sir.
I'd like five of those.
That'll be a thousand yen.
Thousand yen?
In the Middle East,
Japanese and Western business
practices are by no means universal.
Namely, prices change and
are open to negotiation.
With no understanding of how to
haggle or how to value goods for sale,
first-time visitors can become
easy targets for exploitation.
But here, people don't see such
exploitation as a bad thing.
The swindled are deserving of
the label fool, not victim.
Haggling takes guts and ingenuity.
Really?
The first step is the art of the bluff.
Make it clear you see through the trick.
Let him know you're no slouch.
Don't mock me now.
That's far too much for
a handful of kebabs.
A hearty laugh always helps.
Then, how much would you buy him for?
The merchant will test the waters.
Make it 250 yen for five.
In return, you throw out a price so low?
You can't help but blush and then!
He'll act as if you have no
sense at all catching on?
If I sold them for that cheap,
I'd be out on the streets!
my wife and seven children
would starve to death!
Then he'll gesture the old throat slash,
but you can't give up the fight just yet!
Then maybe I'll just
buy them somewhere else?
pretend that you're leaving.
Okay, friend, you win.
I'm very much like foreigners.
I'll sell you five for 700 yen.
He'll try to stop you.
Then make it 300!
Let the haggling begin! 600!
350! 550!
400! 450!
425! I'll take him!
Alright, I got them for less than
half his original price. Take that!
I'm made out like a bandit.
and just as you think you won.
I usually sell five for 150
yen. Bye-bye. Thank you, sir.
Holy crap! Turn around!
That old lady's awake!
I...
I promised you.
I haven't said anything
to any of them, I swear.
Why are you here?
What could you possibly want with me?
Did you think I would actually tell
them the secret of Lord Dio's stand?
I am and shall always
be his loyal servant!
Gross! What are they?
Some kind of worms?
Why?
I have done nothing wrong!
Why have you come here to kill me?
Lord Dio places his trust in no one.
Not even you and Yabba.
That is why.
And it's my job to make sure
that you never speak again.
As for the rest of you...
The only way you're leaving is in pieces.
Mime!
What?
You can call me Dan.
Dan of Steel.
My stand represents the
one and only Lover's Card.
I will see to it that you all meet the
same fate as that pathetic witch Iniyaba.
How could you?
That old lady was one of your
own, you son of a... Memory!
Lies!
These are all lies!
This isn't happening.
Lord Dio would never do this to me.
I am his loyal servant.
Loyal!
These things coming out of her body,
they're definitely not some stand.
Don't you see it?
They're actual tentacles.
I have dedicated everything to him.
Lord Dio would never do me such harm.
He'd never plant a flesh bud in me.
What did she say?
Lord Dio is my only reason for living.
We trust each other wholeheartedly.
Hold on!
See that?
The sun just disintegrated them.
The flesh bud.
It's made out of Dio's own cells.
Precisely.
I must say you were
quite the perceptive one.
Since you're so astute, I'll continue.
This is what a full-grown
flesh bud looks like.
I want to kill her, not control her.
So I just grew it inside the old bag.
And yarba,
you may be the very one who told lord
dio about the stance but you're a
fool to think that a man with such
complete power would ever trust a feeble
old woman like you unfortunately
it's a point you fail to realize old
lady what's the true identity of dio
stan tell us you placed all your hope
in dio you trusted him with your
life and your sons and now after all
you've sacrificed you know he's not
the man you thought he was you know i'm
right we must defeat dio no matter
the cost you have to tell us we need
to know tell us what we need to know
about dio's stand before it's too late
oh my lord
he believes in me
so i'll serve him even in
death i won't betray him
Oh, God!
How pathetic.
It's laughable how sad that old woman was.
But the very depth of her trust
in him should tell you something.
Lord Dio's evil charm is more
powerful than you can imagine.
The old woman may have had it out for us,
but she was misled and
sure as hell didn't deserve
that death.
I'll see you join her.
Four against one, but we won't hold back.
Prepare yourself,
Dan.
On your feet.
Hey, jackass.
Stop trying to act cool
and get up and fight.
This is going down whether
you want it or not. Go ahead.
But you can't touch me.
I'm Dan of
Steel and none of you can take me down.
You don't have what it takes.
What the?
What What happened, Mr.
Joestar?
He flew back just like that guy.
You're an utter fool.
I was about to explain my
powers when you hit me.
That impatience nearly
killed your grandfather.
I suggest you listen next time.
Listen.
My job's not over.
I have other important
business to attend to.
You really think I would show my
face here just to kill in Yaba?
You...
you damn bastard!
You told us that your stand is
the lover's, isn't that right?
So tell us!
What the hell does it do?
What's the point in telling you
now the battle's already begun, Mr.
Joestar?
You're all simpletense.
You do know no matter how hard you
look, you won't be able to see my stand.
Hey, Half-Pine.
You want some cash?
It's all yours if he can hit
me in the leg with that broom.
What?
But why would he?
Now hit me!
The hell? Now what?
It hurts!
I don't get it!
It's like I broke my leg!
You mean you still haven't figured it out?
That's so disappointing.
My stand can't be seen because
it's rooted firmly inside you.
The moment Inyaba died, it entered you.
It got to your brain through your
ear, and that's how I'll get to you.
My stand and I are
connected, just like yours.
If my stand gets hurt, so do I,
and the reverse is also true.
You're utterly helpless.
If you so much as scratch me,
in that instant,
my stand will react to
my pain by going berserk
in your head and inflicting
the same agony on you.
Not only that, it will deliver
a pain several times greater.
Now, I'll say it once more.
Alone or together, you won't be
able to lay a single finger on me.
Plus, the Lovers has taken one of
Lord Dio's flesh buds into your body.
It's growing in your brain as we speak.
Just like it did to Inyaba.
It'll devour you from the inside out.
I don't recall asking you to strike
me again, you stupid little brat!
Well, to be honest, my stand of lovers
isn't as strong as you might think it'd be.
It doesn't have the strength to
move even a single strand of hair,
making it the world's weakest stand.
However, power isn't necessary if all
you want to do is kill your opponent.
Do you understand, gentlemen?
Say something unfortunate happens.
Like I get into an accident, a baseball
hits me, or I just trip and fall.
How do you think that would
affect you, Mr. Joestar?
I might get banged up some, but your body
would suffer far greater pain than mine.
What the? How?
How am I feeling your knuckles
cracking in my prosthetic hand?
You've got ten minutes, old man.
Then your brain will be eaten through
and you'll be a corpse like in Yabba.
Jotaro, calm down.
Don't do anything rash.
Sorry, but no.
I'm gonna kill this damn tool so quickly.
You won't have enough time to feel pain
Kill me before I feel it,
huh? Sounds interesting.
Do it then.
I want to see what happens
What are you waiting for, Jotaro?
Come on, let's see it.
Just what were you planning to strike?
Tell me my face or maybe my throat
What? You mad?
Let's see what'll happen.
Don't back down on me now, man.
Why don't you try busting
a hole through my chest?
Or how about you give up on using your
stand and crack my head open with a rock?
This one looks like a prime specimen.
It sure looks big enough for the job.
You do not want to
underestimate me, pretty boy.
When I say I'm gonna
do something, I do it.
Jotaro!
Don't do it!
You've already seen how
effective his power is.
Are you trying to kill
your own grandfather?
Uh, this is Jotaro we're talking about.
He might be.
You dumb good-for-nothing punk.
Yotaro!
Don't you toy with me, you bastard.
After the geezer kicks
the bucket, you're next.
Look out!
It'll be your brain that I send
the lovers in to kill. Stop!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
This is just insane.
My grandson is being beaten up to save me.
We're completely at this guy's mercy.
I can't do anything
while it's in my brain.
I remember when that poison ring
was placed around my aorta long ago.
But think, Joseph.
There's got to be something you can do.
Hey!
Chotaro!
Keep him away from Mr.
Joestar at all costs!
We're gonna try and get as
far away from him as possible!
I see.
So that's your plan?
Putting some distance
between me and the old man
might make my Stan's power
vanish without a trace?
Sorry, but my Stan's physical
weakness is made up for in other ways.
The Lovers may be physically weak,
but its range is farther
than any Stan in existence.
It doesn't matter how far they
run, their lives are forfeit,
as long as it remains in a host.
What's up?
Hey, Jotaro, I'm talking to you.
It's impolite not to look at people
when they're speaking to you.
Look at me!
What's wrong?
You sound like you're
starting to lose your cool.
What's your plan?
Follow me around till
Grandpa Joseph keels over?
Sounds like a blast.
Den of steel, was it?
I'll make you pay for this,
just a matter of when.
Well,
if you're gonna stick around for a while,
I might as well help
myself to your wallet.
Nothing but chump change, huh?
Though I didn't expect a guy like
you to be sporting a tog hoyer.
I'll be borrowing this.
There!
An electronics store! Mr.
Joestar! They have TVs!
Yeah, so?
Why does that matter now?
Come on, Polnareff.
Did you really think we were running away?
I'm going to fight this blasted
stand that's inside my head.
Fight?
Mon Dieu, non!
We only have a few minutes, and we're
going to need your help to pull this off.
Huh?
Hermit Purple!
That's it!
Oh, no!
I hoped he was bluffing.
How the hell did he get inside
my brain so damn quickly?
Wow.
If I hadn't seen it myself,
I wouldn't have believed it.
At least now we know for
sure that it's in there.
But I still don't see how we're
going to destroy the thing.
By having our stands enter Mr.
Joestar's ear canal to find
and destroy the monster.
Are you crazy?
Stands are simply
materializations of energy.
We should be able to shrink them.
You don't know that.
Hey, try not to break anything
while you're in there.
There's no time.
We're going in now, Polnareff.
Uh, all right.
I revenge green!
Silver Chilliots!
Smaller.
Get smaller.
We're going to be entering a blood vessel.
Right.
A drainage ditch.
This could be fun.
I'd try to jump it, but if
I trip and twist my ankle,
it could be real bad for old man Joestar.
Walking all the way to that
bridge would be such a bother.
I've got an idea.
Lie down across this ditch and
make yourself into a bridge.
I'll just walk on you to get across.
What now?
You don't want to be
my bridge or something?
Yeah, shut up.
What the hell do you keep yammering about?
I said make yourself into a bridge!
You good for nothing, Eric!
What?
What's the matter? Mr. Joestar!
My leg!
It's going numb!
Dammit, Jotaro!
What the hell are you doing?
Ah, don't look so upset, Jotaro.
Come on.
I don't have all day, you know.
Good.
You're a rather sturdy bridge, aren't you?
Bang, Bang, Bang, impressive.
Hold on.
Almost there.
Mr.
Joestar, I think the stand is here.
Hiding around the thalamus
makes the most sense.
That's the point where
the nervous system begins.
Polnareff and I will enter a blood
vessel from inside your inner ear,
then swim through the
veins toward the brainstem.
But to do that, we need to tear the
wall of the blood vessel. Hey! Hold on!
You're using your stance!
Can't you just slip through
it without cutting me?
At this size, it's not possible.
The blood vessel's wall is too thick.
The slit will be microscopic, so there'll
be no hemorrhaging to worry about.
The only other issue is time.
Cutting through a blood vessel or nerve
right now will take
several minutes at least.
Otherwise, the lovers would have
already done its damage by now.
Though, in all probability,
it may have already started.
Keeping our stands this
tiny is really exhausting.
It's taking a ton of stand power
just to get where we can fight.
Oni va!
Oh my god!
I really don't feel so well.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Foreign types of the hookah. I say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses.
Take their trays. Spin around.
And they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
Oh, hey, oh?
You drop, you drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say. Walk
like
an Egyptian.
I have a very nasty itch.
I'm in such a good mood
I can hardly stand it.
I want you to use your
tongue to shine them.
To win in life, one must
thoroughly know oneself.
The spoils belong to those who
admit their own weaknesses!